DILLON BORDELEAU

DETAILS

PHONE

343-543-8008

EMAIL

DillonBordeleau@gmail.com

LINKS

<u>LinkedIn</u>

PROFILE

Driven and accomplished support professional with more than 3 years of sales and 9 years of customer service and technical support experience. Seeking full-time employment where I will ideally get to work in a team environment and excel as a key player on your client/customer-facing team.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Retail Support Specialist, Shopify

Mar 2020 — August 2023

- Worked directly with Shopify store owners and Shopify support advisors/ technical support teams to resolve escalated retail tickets.
- Troubleshot various features of the Shopify e-commerce platform, Shopify POS App and Shopify retail hardware during live interactions with Shopify merchants on phones, chats and emails.
- Analyzed stores' traffic, conversion rate and returning customer metrics to provide tailored business coaching and enterprise growth solutions.
- Thrived in a team environment to provide the very best technical and continuing customer support in the e-commerce industry.

Mobile Advisor (Sales), The Mobile Shop

Jun 2017 — Apr 2019

- · Pursued leads to create opportunities and meet quarterly sales quotas.
- Worked face-to-face with customers to provide service and address their mobile concerns/needs.
- Worked with every major service provider in Ontario to provide service to their customers, including managing customer accounts with proprietary software.
- Tracked performance against sales targets and went above and beyond to reach store and district goals.

Director of Fundraising, Carleton Neuroscience Society

Sep 2016 — Jan 2020

- Designing and executing events to raise funds for the society, including day of operations.
- Collaborated with charities, local businesses and the university to raise awareness and money for various mental health related causes.
- Recruiting general members and managing them and their concerns on a daily basis.

EDUCATION

B.Sc Neuroscience, Carleton University

Jan 2016 — Jun 2021

- · Dean's Honour List 2017, 2018, 2019, 2020.
- · Golden Key International Honour's Society Member.
- Independent Undergraduate Researcher in the Chee Lab.

PUBLICATIONS

Sankhe, Bordeleau, Alfonso, Wittman & Chee (2022). Loss of Glutamatergic Signalling from MCH neurons reduced anxiety-like behaviour in Novel Environments. *Journal of Neuroendicrinology*, 35(1).

https://doi.org/10.1111/jne.13222 | https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36529144/